[
  {
    "id": "381",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS allows you to create storage volumes and attach them to _____?",
      "answers": [
        "EC2 instances",
        "S3",
        "Route 53",
        "Elastic Load Balancers"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "382",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Once EBS volumes are attached to an EC2 instance, you can do which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "create a file system ontop of the EBS volumes",
        "run a database ontop of the EBS volumes",
        "use them in any way you would use block storage",
        "use them in any way you would use object storage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["create a file system ontop of the EBS volumes", "run a database ontop of the EBS volumes", "use them in any way you would use block storage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "383",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which are true about EBS volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "they are placed within a specific AZ where they are automatically replicated within that AZ",
        "they are placed within a specific AZ where they are automatically replicated to a different AZ",
        "they are placed within a specific AZ but not replicated",
        "they are dirrecty attached to your EC2 instance and not replicated"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["they are placed within a specific AZ where they are automatically replicated within that AZ"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "384",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS is which type of storage?",
      "answers": [
        "block based",
        "object based"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["block based"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "385",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 5",
      "question": "Which are the types of EBS volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["General Purpose SSD (GP2)", "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)", "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)", "Cold HDD (SC1)", "Magnetic Standard"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "386",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type balances both price and performance?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["General Purpose SSD (GP2)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "387",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type has a ratio of 3 IOPS per GB with up to 10,000 IOPS?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["General Purpose SSD (GP2)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "388",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type can burst up to 3,000 IOPS for extended periods of time for volumes at 3,334 GB and above?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["General Purpose SSD (GP2)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "389",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type is designed for I/O intensive applications such as large relational databases or NoSQL databases?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "390",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type would you use if you need more than 10,000 IOPS?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "391",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type allows you to provision up to 20,000 IOPS per volume?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "392",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type would you use for big data storage?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "393",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type would you use for data warehouse storage?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "394",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type would you use for log processing?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "395",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which EBS volume types cannot be boot volumes?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)", "Cold HDD (SC1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "396",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type is the lowest cost for infrequently accessed workloads?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cold HDD (SC1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "397",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type would you use for file servers?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cold HDD (SC1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "398",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume is the lowest cost per gigabyte of all EBS volumes that is bootable?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Magnetic Standard"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "399",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type is ideal for workloads where data is accessed infrequently, and applications where the lowest cost is important?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Magnetic Standard"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "400",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Spot EC2 instances, if YOU terminate the instance ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "you pay for the hour in which it was terminated",
        "AWS gives the hour in which it was terminated for free",
        "you pay for the fraction of the hour in which you ran the instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["you pay for the hour in which it was terminated"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "401",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Spot EC2 instances, if AWS terminates the instance ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "you pay for the hour in which it was terminated",
        "AWS gives the hour in which it was terminated for free",
        "you pay for the fraction of the hour in which you ran the instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS gives the hour in which it was terminated for free"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "402",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which EBS volume type is good for sequentially written data, like log files?",
      "answers": [
        "General Purpose SSD (GP2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (IO1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)",
        "Cold HDD (SC1)",
        "Magnetic Standard",
        "Optical Standard"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Throughput Optimized HDD (ST1)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "403",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You cannot mount 1 EBS volume to multiple EC2 instances?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "404",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you wish to mount a volume to multiple EC2 instances you should use which type of disk service?",
      "answers": [
        "EBS",
        "EFS",
        "ECS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EFS"]
    }
  }
]
